{
    "id": "89019ece5d844f6b8a611331e3a39372",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He did not ………………………….. to my letter.",
            "description": "Respond is the verb here.",
            "answers": [
                "respond",
                "response",
                "responsive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think there is any ……………………….. for you to come again.",
            "description": "Necessity is the noun here. We need a noun after any.",
            "answers": [
                "necessity",
                "necessary",
                "necessitate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Though his early attempts were not ………………………….., he did not lose heart.",
            "description": "Successful is the adjective here.  It is used as the complement of the subject early attempts. ",
            "answers": [
                "success",
                "successful",
                "succeed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What a ………………………….. performance!",
            "description": "We need an adjective before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "fascination",
                "fascinating"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The master’s ………………………………. had great effect on his disciple.",
            "description": "Exhortation means urging or persuasion. ",
            "answers": [
                "exhort",
                "exhortion",
                "exhortation"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The government should take the …………………………… to help poor people displaced by natural calamities.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "initiate",
                "initiation",
                "initiative"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The lawyer was not able to ……………………………. his arguments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "substance",
                "substantiate",
                "substantiative"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He completed the work to the ………………………….. of his boss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "satisfy",
                "satisfied",
                "satisfaction"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What I like the most about you is your ……………………………….",
            "description": "Simplicity is the noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "simplicity",
                "simplified"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have no …………………………… towards anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hostile",
                "hostilities"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ……………………………….. expertise in building low cost homes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "consider",
                "considerate",
                "considerable"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I pay them an …………………………….. visit.",
            "description": "Occasion is a noun occasional is the adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}